<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>Pharmacist: Represcribed</name>
    <authors>
		<li>Ceres</li>
		<li>Fluffy</li>
	</authors>
    <packageId>Fluffy.Pharmacist</packageId>
    <description>A continuation of the lovely mod Pharmacist, originally created by Fluffy. For a full description of what the mod does, you can consult the original page, but in short: Pharmacist allows you to set the maximum level of medicine that can be used for different severities of injury. Doctors will use the best medicine available, depending on the target's allowed medical care and configured settings.

&lt;size=28&gt;Changes to the original&lt;/size&gt;
Pharmacist: Represcribed makes a number of tweaks and improvements to the original Pharmacist:
* Slaves and entities have their own tending settings. Naturally, they will only appear if Ideology and Anomaly are active, respectively.
* Added an "Ongoing conditions" category. This includes non-fatal diseases like gut worms and fibrous mechanites, but also includes long-term conditions like blood rot and asthma; in general, anything that requires repeated tending to mitigate will fall under this category (although dangerous diseases like plague, flu, etc. are still categorized using the old system depending on their severity.) These were all previously treated as minor injuries.
* Doctors can be configured to only attempt to search for medicine in a specific radius. If they can't find any medicine close enough, they'll just use the next best thing they have on hand (or nothing at all).

&lt;size=28&gt;Aren't there a few existing revivals of Pharmacist?&lt;/size&gt;
There are! None of them do what this one does, though. Both the original Pharmacist and all of its unofficial updates weren't ever truly modernized, even though they worked on newer versions of RimWorld. Some specific glaring issues like blood rot received fixes on a case-by-case basis, but long-standing pain points (i.e. diseases like gut worms being treated as minor injuries even though they can seriously hamstring a colony) were never addressed.

Represcribed aims to be a proper modernization of the original Pharmacist, not just a resuscitation to keep it functional across versions. RimWorld's gotten a lot more complex since 2018, and the Pharmacist's advice should too! 

</description>
    <url>https://github.com/fluffy-mods/Pharmacist</url>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.6</li>
    </supportedVersions>
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
            <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>